disinfo.com 2016-10-18

# Privacy - disinformation

### Revision Date: October 14, 2009

The Disinformation Company Ltd. (“Disinformation”) values the users of our website (the “Website”). Your privacy and trust are very important to us. We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of the personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that we collect when you use the Website and the services offered on the Website (“Disinformation Services”). This Privacy Policy describes the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it. By using the Website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us using our [Contact Form](http://disinfo.com/?page_id=7).

### Does Disinformation Ever Make Changes to its Privacy Policy?

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. If you receive notification of a change in our Privacy Policy, you must review the new Privacy Policy carefully to make sure you understand our practices and procedures. You may not be able to receive notices from us if your cookies are not set to accept and/or are disabled.

### What Types of Information Does Disinformation Collect From Me?

**Personal Information**. We and/or our service provider partners may collect any Personal Information that you provide to us, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and credit card number, as well as the Internet protocol (IP) Address from which you post stories and/or comments to the Website.

**Non-Personal Information.** We do not currently collect non-personal information from you, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous website you visited, your ISP or operating system (“Non-Personal Information”). Non-Personal Information cannot be easily used to personally identify you. 

### How and When Does Disinformation Collect This Information?

**Providing Information to Us.** We collect Personal Information from you when you provide it to us. For example, if you purchase a product sold through our store, we or our store fulfillment partner may collect your name, mailing address, telephone number, credit card number, and email address. If you sign up to receive a newsletter or to contribute stories or comments to the Website, we will collect your email address and we register your Internet protocol (IP) Address.

**Communications With Us.** If you communicate with us regarding the Website or the Disinformation Services, we will collect any information that you provide to us in any such communication.

**Analytic and Reporting Technologies.** Like the operators of most websites, we use analytic and reporting technologies to record Non-Personal Information such as Internet domain and host names, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser software, operating system types, clickstream patterns, and the dates and times that the Website and the Disinformation Services are accessed. To do this, we may use web beacons and cookies, including those from third parties.

### How Does Disinformation Use My Information?

**Personal Information.** We use Personal Information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving the Disinformation Services and the Website, fulfilling requests for information, producing and shipping the products that you order, and providing customer support. Similarly, if you sign up to receive a Disinformation newsletter, we will use the email address you provide to send you the newsletters.

**Non-Personal Information.** If at any time we collect it, we may use Non-Personal Information to track the use of the Website and the Disinformation Services and for other internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving the Disinformation Services and the Website.

### When Will Disinformation Disclose My Information to Third Parties?

**Disclosure to Successors.** We may disclose your Personal Information to any successor-in-interest of ours, such as a company that acquires us. In the event Disinformation goes through a business transition, such as a merger or acquisition by or with another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or by a notice on our Website of any such change in ownership or control of your Personal Information.

**Disclosure to Unaffiliated Third Parties.** We may disclose your Personal Information to prevent an emergency, to prevent harm to others, to respond to legal requirements, to protect or enforce our rights and policies, to protect or enforce the rights of a third party, or as required or permitted by law (including, without limitation, to comply with a subpoena or court order).

**Disclosure to Third Party Service Providers and Online Partners.** We may contract with various third parties who help us provide, maintain and improve the Website and the Disinformation Services. For example, we use a third party to operate and manage our online store, including the processing of payments and fulfillment of products, and we may subcontract out production, analytics, reporting or other operations. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent such third parties from disclosing your Personal Information, except for the purpose of providing the services in question. We cannot guarantee that such third parties will not disclose your Personal Information.

**Disclosure of Non-Personal Information.** We will disclose Non-Personal Information, in aggregate form, to potential strategic partners, advertisers, investors, customers, and others. You may not opt-out of the sharing of this information. However, it cannot be easily used to identify you personally.

### What About Cookies and Web Beacons?

A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. Most websites use cookies. We use cookies to track your use of the Website and the Disinformation Services, provide you with a more personalized user experience, and to allow you to login and begin use of the Disinformation Services automatically when you visit the Website.

A web beacon is an often-transparent graphic image, usually no larger than a 1_1 pixel that is placed on a web page or in an e-mail that is used to monitor the behavior of the user visiting the Website or receiving the e-mail.

Cookies and web beacons used by Disinformation and our online partners are not linked to Personal Information.

### Does Disinformation Protect My Personal Information?

**Personal Information.** Whenever we obtain your Personal Information, we use commercially reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, we are not insurers of the security of your Personal Information. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control.

**Website Content.** The content that you store, post, or transmit on or through the Website, such as message board postings, may be accessed by other users, including people that you do not know. We are not responsible for the actions of others. Therefore, you should use care in communicating with other users and only disclose your Personal Information to other users that you know to be trustworthy. You should not assume that your content will be kept private.

**Security.** The security of your Personal Information is important to us. Our policy is to require our third party service providers, such as the online store and personals providers, to encrypt sensitive information such as a credit card numbers using secure socket layer technology (SSL). However, we cannot guarantee compliance with this policy and no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Does This Privacy Policy Apply When I Access Third Party Websites?

You may be able to access third party websites directly from the Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply when you access third party websites. We cannot control how third parties may use Personal Information you disclose to them, so you should carefully review the privacy policy of any third party website you visit before using it or disclosing your Personal Information to its provider.

### What About Children’s Privacy?

**Under Thirteen.** The Disinformation Services are intended for users ages 13 and older only. Accordingly, we will not knowingly collect or use any Personal Information from children that we know to be under the age of 13. In addition, we will delete any information in our database that we know originates from a child under the age of 13.

**Thirteen to Seventeen.** Prospective users between the ages of 13 and 17 can only use the Disinformation Services under their parents or legal guardian’s supervision. If you are between the ages of 13 and 17, you, your parent, or your legal guardian may request that we deactivate any of your Personal Information in our database and/or opt-out from receiving communications from us. If you wish to do so, please contact us using our [Contact Form](http://disinfo.com/?page_id=7).

### Can I Opt-Out From Receiving Communications From Disinformation?

We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of having your Personal Information used for certain purposes. For example, you can unsubscribe from any email newsletter list at any time by clicking on a link provided in all email newsletters sent to you. If you purchase a product in our store but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material, you can indicate your preference on our store partner’s order form.

If we disclose your Personal Information to a third party in a manner that is not set forth in this Privacy Policy you will be notified so that you can make an informed choice about sharing your Personal Information with that third party.

### How To Contact Us: 

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email using our [Contact Form](http://disinfo.com/?page_id=7).

Written queries may be sent to:  
The Disinformation Company Ltd.  
111 East 14th Street, Suite 108  
New York NY 10003
